Guide to the Walter Lowenfels Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Correspondence, 1920-1979; Series I; 21; (50 boxes)
  - General Correspondence, 1925-1976
    - Fitzgerald, F. Scott (Francis Scott), 1932 (Box 11, Folder 225)
      Photocopy of correspondence.
    - Flanner, Janet, undated (Box 11, Folder 226)
    - Fles, Barthold, 1961-1963 (Box 11, Folder 227)
    - Flores, Angel, 1958-1974, undated (Box 11, Folder 228)
    - Flynn, Elizabeth Gurley, 1958-1959 (Box 11, Folder 229)
    - Folkways, 1957-1967 (Box 12, Folder 230)
    - Folsom, Franklin, 1955-1971 (Box 12, Folder 231)
    - Folsom, Michael, 1967-1972 (Box 12, Folder 232)
    - Ford, Hugh, 1962-1975 (Box 12, Folder 233-234)
    - Foreign Language Press, 1954-1967 (Box 12, Folder 235)
    - Foreign Literature, 1955-1964, undated (Box 12, Folder 236)
    - Fort Hood Defense Committee, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 237)
    - Fortner, Ethel, 1967-1972 (Box 12, Folder 238)
    - Fraenkel, Michael, 1930-1951, undated (Box 12, Folder 239-245)
    - Frank, Waldo David, 1955-1965 (Box 12, Folder 246)
    - Frederick A. Praeger, Inc., 1963 (Box 12, Folder 247)
    - Free Lance Poets and Prose Workshop, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 248)
      Includes letters from Russell Atkins.
    - Freedomways, 1961-1963 (Box 12, Folder 249)
    - Friesen, Gordon, 1969-1971, undated1 (Box 12, Folder 250)
    - Fulton, Len, 1967-1974 (Box 12, Folder 251)
    - "G" General, 1953-1975, undated (Box 13, Folder 252-253)
    - Gaess, Roger, 1970-1975, undated (Box 13, Folder 254)
    - Gardner, Carl, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 255)
    - Gardos, Grace, 1965-1967 (Box 13, Folder 256)
    - Geddes, Jeff, 1974-1976 (Box 13, Folder 257)
    - Geismar, Maxwell, 1954-1976, undated (Box 13, Folder 258)
    - Georgakas, Dan, 1970-1975, undated (Box 13, Folder 259)
    - George Braziller, Inc., 1963-1975 (Box 13, Folder 260)
    - George, Wilton A., 1969-1970, undated (Box 13, Folder 261)
    - Gershgoren, Estelle, 1962-1968, undated (Box 13, Folder 262)
    - Gibson, Morgan, 1965-1969, undated (Box 13, Folder 263)
    - Gill, John, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 264)
    - Ginsberg, Allen, 1959-1968, undated (Box 13, Folder 265)
    - Gitlin, Todd, 1966-67, undated (Box 13, Folder 266)
    - Gold, Mike, 1951-1967, undated (Box 13, Folder 267)
    - Goldsmith, Walter, 1953, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 268)
    - Goldwater, Walter, 1963-1975, undated (Box 13, Folder 269)
    - Goodman, Ronald, 1956-1968, undated (Box 13, Folder 270)
    - Gordon, Midi, 1953-1975, undated (Box 13, Folder 271)
    - Gotham Book Mart, 1957-1968, undated (Box 13, Folder 272)
    - Gover, Robert, 1962-1968, undated (Box 13, Folder 273)
    - Green, Gil, 1966, undated (Box 14, Folder 274)
    - Greinke, Eric, 1975, undated (Box 14, Folder 275)
    - Gross, Ronald, 1967-1976, undated (Box 14, Folder 276-277)
    - Grossman, Richard, 1964-1975, undated (Box 14, Folder 278)
    - Grove Press, 1963-1966, undated (Box 14, Folder 279)
    - Grundberg, Andy, 1970-1972, undated (Box 14, Folder 280)
    - Guthrie, Woody, circa 1954-1961 (Box 14, Folder 281)
    - Guttman, Allen, 1964-1970, undated (Box 14, Folder 282)
    - Gwynn, Donald Grafton, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 283)
    - "H" General, 1958-1976, undated (Box 14, Folder 284-286)
    - Hahn, Hannelore, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 287)
    - Hall, Byron C. (Byron Carlyle), 1964-1971 (Box 14, Folder 288)
    - Hanna, Charles Shahoud, 1962-1965 (Box 14, Folder 289)
    - Harper, Michael, 1970, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 290)
    - Harper & Row, Publishers, 1963-1973, undated (Box 14, Folder 291)
    - Harris, Emily Katharine, 1965-1972, undated (Box 14, Folder 292)
    - Harris, Marguerite, 1961-1967, undated (Box 14, Folder 293)
    - Harvey, Louise, 1955-1957, undated (Box 14, Folder 294)
    - Hays, Lee, 1945-1964, undated (Box 14, Folder 295-296)
    - Heard, Nathan, 1969-1970 (Box 15, Folder 297)
    - Hedley, Leslie Woolf, 1957-1971, undated (Box 15, Folder 298-299)
    - Heinrich, Helmut, 1961-1967, undated (Box 15, Folder 300)
    - Henderson, David, 1962-1971, undated (Box 15, Folder 301)
    - Henry Miller Literary Society, 1960-1962 (Box 15, Folder 302)
    - Heritage Printers, 1962-1964 (Box 15, Folder 303)
    - Hernton, Calvin C., 1963-1968 (Box 15, Folder 304)
    - Hicks, Granville, 1938 (Box 15, Folder 305)
    - Hill and Wang, 1963-1966, undated (Box 15, Folder 306)
    - Hill, Hyacinthe, 1968-1973 (Box 15, Folder 307)
    - Hille, Waldemar, 1954, 1965, undated (Box 15, Folder 308)
    - Himmersky, Krassin, 1973-1975, undated (Box 15, Folder 309)
    - Hines, Carl Wendell, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 310)
    - Hogan, Homer, 1971-1973 (Box 15, Folder 311)
    - Holt, Rinehart, and Winston, inc., 1963-1968 (Box 15, Folder 312)
    - Horizon Press, 1963-1971 (Box 15, Folder 313)
      Includes letters from Ben Raeburn.
    - Hosein, Clyde, 1959-1969, undated (Box 15, Folder 314)
    - Hughes, Langston, 1960-1968, undated (Box 15, Folder 315)
    - Hugot, Francois, 1959-1973, undated (Box 15, Folder 316-317)
    - Hugot, Shirley, 1961-1962, undated (Box 15, Folder 318)
    - Human Voice Quarterly, 1965-1971, undated (Box 15, Folder 319)
      Includes letters from D. V. Smith.
    - "I" General, 1930-1975, undated (Box 16, Folder 320)
    - I. F. Stone, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 321)
    - Ignatow, David, 1960-1973 (Box 16, Folder 322)
    - Imprimerie Sainte-Catherine S.A., 1958 (Box 16, Folder 323)
    - Independent, 1962-1966 (Box 16, Folder 324)
    - Inez, Colette, 1967-1972 (Box 16, Folder 325)
    - Inman, Will, 1963-1975 (Box 16, Folder 326)
    - International Publishers
      - Allen, James S., 1958-1973, undated (Box 16, Folder 327-328)
      - Auerback, Isabelle, 1964-1972 (Box 16, Folder 329)
      - Diskin, Lou, 1972-1975 (Box 16, Folder 330)
      - General, 1964-1974 (Box 16, Folder 331)
    - Irrera, Judy, 1965-1966, undated (Box 16, Folder 332)
    - Ivan Obolensky, Inc., 1963-1964 (Box 16, Folder 333)
    - "J" General, 1955-1976, undated (Box 16, Folder 334)
    - Jackson, Gerald, 1966-1968, undated (Box 16, Folder 335)
    - Jacobs, Judy (Lowenfels), 1958-1966, undated (Box 16, Folder 336)
    - Jacobs, Stretch, 1960-1964 (Box 16, Folder 337)
    - Jerome, Alice, 1965-1968 (Box 16, Folder 338)
    - Jewish Currents, 1954-1969 (Box 16, Folder 339)
      Formerly Jewish Life.
    - Jodorosky, Raquel, 1965-1968, undated (Box 17, Folder 340)
    - Johnson, Joe, 1963-1966, undated (Box 17, Folder 341)
    - Johnson, Kay, 1960-1963, undated (Box 17, Folder 342)
    - Jones, Leroi, 1959-1968 (Box 17, Folder 343)
      Includes letter from Conrad Lynn
    - Jordan, June, 1967-1974, undated (Box 17, Folder 344)
    - Joseph, Cliff, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 345)
    - Josephson, Hannah, 1960-1965 (Box 17, Folder 346)
    - de Jouvenel, Renaud, 1960-1961 (Box 17, Folder 347)
    - Juin, Hubert, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 348)
    - "K" General, 1954-1975, undated (Box 17, Folder 349)
    - Kalugin, David, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 350)
    - Kane, Gary, 1967-1975 (Box 17, Folder 351)
    - Kane, Michal Lowenfels, 1935-1975, undated (Box 17, Folder 352-353)
    - Kane, Tamsie, 1965-1975, undated (Box 17, Folder 354)
    - Kaplan, Jonathan, 1965-1975, undated (Box 17, Folder 355)
    - Kaplan, Philip, 1958-1975, undated (Box 17, Folder 356)
    - Katz, Elia, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 357)
    - Katz, Helen, 1935 (Box 17, Folder 358)
    - Kayak, 1964-1970 (Box 17, Folder 359)
      Includes letters from George Hitchcock
    - Keith, William, 1964-1970 (Box 18, Folder 360)
    - Kenin, Millea, 1967-1970 (Box 18, Folder 361)
    - Kent, Rockwell, 1954-1971 (Box 18, Folder 362)
    - Kessler, Stephen, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 363)
    - Kittredge, Selwyn, 1963-1964, undated (Box 18, Folder 364)
    - Klaristenfeld, Mickey, 1964-1965, undated (Box 18, Folder 365)
    - Klugman, Marianthe, 1958-1964 (Box 18, Folder 366)
    - Koertge, Ronald, 1967-1968, undated (Box 18, Folder 367)
    - Kohut, Joel, 1966-1971 (Box 18, Folder 368)
    - Konopacky, Elizabeth, 1973, undated (Box 18, Folder 369)
    - Kramer, Aaron, 1956, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 370)
    - Kreymborg, Albert and Dorothy, 1956-1966 (Box 18, Folder 371)
    - Kulchur, 1963-1964 (Box 18, Folder 372)
      Includes letters from Lita Hornick
    - Kupferberg, Tuli, 1958-1971, undated (Box 18, Folder 373)
    - Kurtz, Aaron, 1958-1974, undated (Box 18, Folder 374)
    - "L" General, 1953-1975, undated (Box 18, Folder 375-378)
    - Lally, Michael, 1967-1975, undated (Box 19, Folder 379)
    - Langman, Ida, 1953-1976, undated (Box 19, Folder 380)
    - Larkin, Eddie, 1971-1972, undated (Box 19, Folder 381)
    - LeRoy, Gaylord, 1967-1972 (Box 19, Folder 382)
    - Larsen, Carl, 1958-1967, undated (Box 19, Folder 383)
    - Larssen, R.E.F., 1960-1968 (Box 19, Folder 384)
    - Laughlin, James, 1959-1967 (Box 19, Folder 385)
    - Lawentman, Leah, 1972-1975, undated (Box 19, Folder 386)
    - Lawrence Hill and Co., Publishers, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 387)
    - Lawson, John Howard, 1957-1968, undated (Box 19, Folder 388)
    - Leon, S. J., 1964-1975, undated (Box 19, Folder 389)
    - Le Sueur, Meridel, 1958, undated (Box 19, Folder 390)
    - Les Lettres Francais, 1954-1959, undated (Box 19, Folder 391)
    - Levertov, Denise, 1964-1975, undated (Box 19, Folder 392)
    - Levitt, Charles, 1953-1975 (Box 19, Folder 393)
    - Levy, D. A., 1966, undated (Box 19, Folder 394)
    - Lewin, Leonard C., 1963 (Box 19, Folder 395)
    - Liberation, 1959-1971, undated (Box 19, Folder 396)
      Includes letters from David McReynolds
    - Library of Congress. Copyright Office, 1953-1966 (Box 19, Folder 397)
    - Lifshin, Lyn, undated (Box 19, Folder 398)
    - Lindeman, Jack, 4958-1973, undated (Box 19, Folder 399)
    - Lindsay, Jack, 1955-1969, undated (Box 19, Folder 400)
    - Lindsey, Karen, 1969-1974, undated (Box 19, Folder 401)
    - Lippincott, Bruce, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 402)
    - Lipton, Lawrence, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 403)
    - Liveright Publishing Corporation, 1963-1974 (Box 19, Folder 404)
    - Lorch, Sue, 1967-1968, undated (Box 20, Folder 405)
    - Louis Rabinowitz Foundation, 1964-1972 (Box 20, Folder 406)
    - Lowenfels, Albert, 1932-1967, undated (Box 20, Folder 407-410)
    - Lowenfels, Albert B., 1966-1976, undated (Box 20, Folder 411)
    - Lowenfels, Corinne, 1938-1969, undated (Box 20, Folder 412)
    - Lowenfels, Frederick C., 1927-1933, undated (Box 20, Folder 413)
    - Lowenfels, Lillian, 1925-1971, undated (Box 20, Folder 414-417)
    - Lowenfels, Lillian, 1925-1971, undated (Box 21, Folder 418-423)
    - "M" General, 1953-1975, undated (Box 21, Folder 424-426)
    - McCarrell, Stuart, 1963-1970, undated (Box 22, Folder 427)
    - McCord, Howard, 1963-1974, undated (Box 22, Folder 428-433)
    - McGrath, Thomas, 1954-1975, undated (Box 22, Folder 434-435)
    - McGraw-Hill Book Company, 1963-1964 (Box 22, Folder 436)
    - MacLeish, Archibald, undated (Box 22, Folder 437)
    - Macmillan & Co., 1962-1971, undated (Box 22, Folder 438)
    - McNamara, Eugene, 1961-1967, undated (Box 22, Folder 439)
    - McReynolds, David, 1959-1974 (Box 22, Folder 440)
    - McWilliams, Carey, 1960-1967 (Box 22, Folder 441)
      The Nation
    - Magil, A. B. (Abraham Bernard), 1937, 1954-1962 (Box 22, Folder 442)
    - Mainstream, 1953-1963, undated (Box 22, Folder 443-444)
    - Major, Clarence, 1965-1975, undated (Box 23, Folder 445-446)
    - Malanga, Gerard, 1963 (Box 23, Folder 447)
    - Mally, Louise, 1962-1975, undated (Box 23, Folder 448)
    - Martinez, Carmen, 1968-1970 (Box 23, Folder 449)
    - Massachusetts Review, 1962-1971, undated (Box 23, Folder 450)
    - May, James B., 1959-1968, undated (Box 23, Folder 451)
    - Melhem, Diana H., 1971-1975 (Box 23, Folder 452)
    - Meltzer, Terre Dov, 1965-1967, undated (Box 23, Folder 453)
    - Mendelsohn, Maurice, 1967-1975, undated (Box 23, Folder 454)
    - Merriam, Eve, 1962-1969, undated (Box 23, Folder 455)
    - Metcalf, Paul C., 1966, undated (Box 23, Folder 456)
    - Meyer, Hershel, 1956-1966 (Box 23, Folder 457)
    - Meyer, June, 1965-1968, undated (Box 23, Folder 458)
    - Meyers, George, 1972-1973 (Box 23, Folder 459)
    - Michel, Lois, 1967-1971 (Box 23, Folder 460)
    - Miller, Henry, 1934-1967 (Box 23, Folder 461)
    - Millet, Martha, 1949-1963 (Box 23, Folder 462)
    - Minority of One, 1963-1968 (Box 23, Folder 463)
      Includes letters from Menachem Arnoni
    - Modesto, Zapata, 1964-1965, undated (Box 23, Folder 464)
    - Mondragon, Sergio, 1964-1967, undated (Box 23, Folder 465)
      See also Randall, Margaret
    - Montgomery, George, 1976, undated (Box 23, Folder 466)
    - Montgomery, John, 1964-1965, undated (Box 23, Folder 467)
    - Moore, Henry, 1966 (Box 23, Folder 468)
    - Morrison, Toni, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 469)
    - Mugar Memorial Library (Boston University). Dept. of Special Collections, 1972-1975, undated (Box 24, Folder 470)
    - Mundelein College, 1968-1969 (Box 24, Folder 471)
    - Murphy, Frank, undated (Box 24, Folder 472)
    - Murray, Pauli, 1963-1968, undated (Box 24, Folder 473)
    - Mussakoff, Vladimir, 1954-1955, undated (Box 24, Folder 474)
    - "N" General, 1931-1975, undated (Box 24, Folder 475-476)
    - Naeve, Virginia, 1964, undated (Box 24, Folder 477)
    - The Nation, 1954-1973, undated (Box 24, Folder 478)
    - National Guardian, 1954-1968, undated (Box 24, Folder 479)
    - Neighbors, Charles, 1972-1975, undated (Box 24, Folder 480)
    - Nelson, Steve, 1952-1960, undated (Box 24, Folder 481-483)
    - Neugass, Myra, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 484)
    - New American Library, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 485)
    - New Directions, 1953-1969 (Box 24, Folder 486)
    - New Orlando Publications, 1962-1968, undated (Box 24, Folder 487)
    - New Republic, 1964-1970, undated (Box 24, Folder 488)
    - New World Review, 1958-1974, undated (Box 24, Folder 489)
    - New York Amsterdam News, 1966-1967 (Box 24, Folder 490)
    - The New York Quarterly, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 491)
    - New York Times, 1959-1971, undated (Box 24, Folder 492)
    - New York Times Book Review, 1963-1970, undated (Box 24, Folder 493)
    - The New Yorker, 1963, 1969 (Box 24, Folder 494)
    - Newberry, Mike, 1960, 1963, undated (Box 24, Folder 495)
    - Nickel Review, 1966-1975, undated (Box 25, Folder 496)
      Includes letters from Walt Shepperd
    - Nin, Anaïs, 1966-1967, undated (Box 25, Folder 497)
    - North, Joe, 1954-1968, undated (Box 25, Folder 498)
    - Nystedt, Bob, 1965-1966 (Box 25, Folder 499)
    - "O" General, 1931-1975, undated (Box 25, Folder 500)
    - Obelisk Books, 1965-1967 (Box 25, Folder 501)
    - O'Connell, Richard, 1965-1974, undated (Box 25, Folder 502)
    - Olmstead, Charles Butch, undated (Box 25, Folder 503)
    - Olympia Press, 1961-1971, undated (Box 25, Folder 504)
    - Oppenheimer, Joel, 1961-1967, undated (Box 25, Folder 505)
    - Ourin, Victor, 1972, undated (Box 25, Folder 506)
    - Outsider, 1960-1965, undated (Box 25, Folder 507)
      Includes letters from Jon Webb
    - "P" General, 1952-1975, undated (Box 25, Folder 508-510)
    - PEN, 1967-1975 (Box 26, Folder 511)
    - Packard, William, 1971-1972 (Box 26, Folder 512)
    - Paidoussi, Eleni, 1971-1972, undated (Box 26, Folder 513)
    - Parsons, Howard, 1966-1976 (Box 26, Folder 514)
    - Partisan Review, 1972-1973 (Box 26, Folder 515)
    - Patterson, William, 1970, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 516)
    - Paul, Jacqueline, 1965, undated (Box 26, Folder 517)
    - Paulhan, M., 1935, undated (Box 26, Folder 518)
    - Payne, Kenneth, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 519)
    - Pembroke Magazine (Box 26)
      - MacLeod, Norman, 1962-1973 (Box 26, Folder 520)
      - Pauli, Ken, 1973-1975 (Box 26, Folder 521)
    - People's World, 1960-1975, undated (Box 26, Folder 522)
    - Pérez, Angel, 1966-1973, undated (Box 26, Folder 523)
    - Perpelitt, Manna (Lowenfels), 1953-1976, undated (Box 26, Folder 524-525)
    - Phoenix Bookshop, 1959-1970 (Box 26, Folder 526)
    - Philip Zinman & Company, 1965-1974 (Box 26, Folder 527)
    - Phillips, Barry, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 528)
    - Piercy, Marge, 1965-1975, undated (Box 26, Folder 529)
    - Planz, Allen, 1963-1968, undated (Box 26, Folder 530)
    - The Poetry Society of America, 1955-1967 (Box 26, Folder 531)
      Includes letters from Gustav Davidson
    - Political Affairs, 1962-1974 (Box 26, Folder 532)
    - Pollak, Felix, 1966-1973 (Box 26, Folder 533)
    - Porter, Bern, 1964-1974, undated (Box 26, Folder 534)
    - Porumbacu, Veronica, 1962-1963, undated (Box 26, Folder 535)
    - Pound, Ezra, 1931, undated (Box 26, Folder 536)
    - Praxis, undated (Box 27, Folder 537)
    - Pritchard, Norman H., 1968 (Box 27, Folder 538)
    - Progress Publishers, 1968-1970 (Box 27, Folder 539)
    - "R" General, 1951-1976, undated (Box 27, Folder 540-542)
    - Radio DDR, 1965, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 543)
    - Rakosi, Carl, 1966-1970 (Box 27, Folder 544)
    - Raman, Yusuf, 1967, undated (Box 27, Folder 545)
    - Randall, Margaret, 1963-1975, undated (Box 27, Folder 546-548)
    - Random House (Firm), 1963-1976, undated (Box 27, Folder 549)
    - Raphael, Lennox, 1964-1967, undated (Box 27, Folder 550)
    - Rasey, Dave, 1965-1966, undated (Box 27, Folder 551)
    - Ray, David, 1965-1972, undated (Box 27, Folder 552)
    - Reaves, Verne, 1970, undated (Box 28, Folder 553)
    - Recht, Jean-Jacques, 1962-1974, undated (Box 28, Folder 554)
    - Redmond, Eugene, 1970, undated (Box 28, Folder 555)
    - Reed, Ishmael, 1964-1976, undated (Box 28, Folder 556)
    - Reeve, Carl, undated (Box 28, Folder 557)
    - Reeve, F. D., 1966-1968, undated (Box 28, Folder 558)
    - Refreiger, Anton, 1958-1973, undated (Box 28, Folder 559)
    - Reinfrank, Arno, 1962, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 560)
    - Reingold, Paula, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 561)
    - Reinstein, Herman, 1964-1965 (Box 28, Folder 562)
    - Rella, Ettore, 1964-1966, undated (Box 28, Folder 563)
    - Renaissance, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 564)
    - Reuss, Dick, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 565)
    - Rexroth, Kenneth, 1937-1970, undated (Box 28, Folder 566)
    - Reznikoff, Charles, 1958-1962, undated (Box 28, Folder 567)
    - Riccio, Ottone, 1967-1972, undated (Box 28, Folder 568)
    - Riding, Laura, 1933, undated (Box 28, Folder 569)
    - Ristau, Harland, 1958-1973, undated (Box 28, Folder 570)
    - Riverside Radio, 1961-1966 (Box 28, Folder 571)
    - Robbins, Doren, 1970, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 572)
    - Roberts, Holland, 1957-1959, undated (Box 28, Folder 573)
    - Roberts, John, 1957, undated (Box 28, Folder 574)
    - Robinson, Earl, 1962-1974, undated (Box 28, Folder 575)
    - Robinson, Eroseanna (Rose), 1960, 1967 (Box 28, Folder 576)
    - Roditi, Edouard, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 577)
    - Rogovin, Mark, 1971, undated (Box 28, Folder 578)
    - Roman Books, 1965-1966, undated (Box 28, Folder 579)
    - Romania. Ambasada (U.S.), 1962-1965 (Box 28, Folder 580)
    - Romanova, Elena, 1964-1966, undated (Box 28, Folder 581)
    - Rosenthal, M. L., 1957-1959 (Box 28, Folder 582)
    - Rubinstein, Annette, 1954-1964, undated (Box 28, Folder 583)
    - Rukeyser, Muriel, 1963-1968 (Box 28, Folder 584)
    - Rust Craft Greeting Cards, 1973-1974 (Box 28, Folder 585)
    - "S" General, 1931-1976, undated (Box 29, Folder 586-591)
    - San Francisco Review, 1958-1963, undated (Box 29, Folder 592)
    - Sanchez, Sonia, 1966-1970, undated (Box 29, Folder 593)
    - Sandidge, Paul, 1960-1968 (Box 29, Folder 594)
    - Saturday Review, 1954-1969, undated (Box 29, Folder 595)
      Includes letters from John Ciardi and Norman Cousins
    - Schechter, Ruth Lisa, 1967-1976, undated (Box 29, Folder 596-597)
    - Schevill, James, 1964-1970 (Box 29, Folder 598)
    - Schlichting, Alex C., 1957-1976, undated (Box 29, Folder 599-600)
    - [Schneider?], Isidore, 1937, undated (Box 30, Folder 601)
    - Schrank, Joe, 1958-1964 (Box 30, Folder 602)
    - Schulman, Howard, 1962-1963 (Box 30, Folder 603)
    - Schwartz, Angela Lowenfels, 1953-1976, undated (Box 30, Folder 604-609)
    - Schwartz, Stephen, 1964-1967, undated (Box 30, Folder 610)
    - Seckar, Alvena, 1954-1975, undated (Box 30, Folder 611)
    - Seeger, Pete, 1951-1976, undated (Box 30, Folder 612-615)
    - Seeger, Toshi, 1964-1971, undated (Box 30, Folder 616)
    - Selby, Hubert, 1956-1964, undated (Box 30, Folder 617)
    - Seven Seas Books, 1958-1969 (Box 30, Folder 618)
    - Shameless Hussy Press, undated (Box 31, Folder 619)
    - Shenandoah, 1963 (Box 31, Folder 620)
    - Sherman, Jane, 1966-1968, undated (Box 31, Folder 621)
    - Shields, Esther and Art, 1968-1976 (Box 31, Folder 622)
    - Shoush, Tawani Wakawa, 1971-1977, undated (Box 31, Folder 623-624)
    - Siegel, Eli, 1957-1969, undated (Box 31, Folder 625)
    - Sigmund, R. J., 1967, undated (Box 31, Folder 626)
    - Silber, Irwin, 1953-1972, undated (Box 31, Folder 627-628)
      Sing Out!
      Oak Publications
    - Simon and Schuster, Inc., 1962-1973, undated (Box 31, Folder 629)
      Includes letters from Elizabeth "Betita" Sutherland
    - Simon, Ruth, 1964-1965 (Box 31, Folder 630)
    - Siqueiros, Angelica Arenal, 1961-1964 (Box 31, Folder 631)
    - Sixeby, George, 1961 (Box 31, Folder 632)
    - Skidmore College, 1965-1968 (Box 31, Folder 633)
    - Slovensky Spisovatel, 1961-1974, undated (Box 31, Folder 634)
    - The Smith, 1969-1975 (Box 31, Folder 635)
    - Smith, Ray, 1968-1976 (Box 31, Folder 636)
    - Snider, Silas, 1964-1975 (Box 31, Folder 637)
    - Snyder, Gary, 1964-1965 (Box 31, Folder 638)
    - Sobsey, Cynthia, 1970-1971, undated (Box 31, Folder 639)
    - Solan, Miriam, 1973-1975 (Box 31, Folder 640)
    - Solano, Solita, 1964 (Box 31, Folder 641)
    - Somerville, John, 1954-1967 (Box 31, Folder 642)
    - Sorrentino, Gil, 1958-1967 (Box 31, Folder 643)
    - South & West, Inc., 1969-1970 (Box 31, Folder 644)
    - Southern Illinois University Press, 1963-1971 (Box 31, Folder 645)
    - Speer, Laurel, 1967 (Box 31, Folder 646)
    - Stanton, Robert, 1966-1967, undated (Box 32, Folder 647)
    - Steiner, Stan, 1959-1971, undated (Box 32, Folder 648-649)
    - Stoller, Joshua, 1970 (Box 32, Folder 650)
    - Stone, Ed, 1965-1976, undated (Box 32, Folder 651-653)
    - Stonehill, 1975-1976, undated (Box 32, Folder 654)
    - Stuart, Lyle, 1964-1970, undated (Box 32, Folder 655)
    - Stuhlman, Gunther, 1966-1968 (Box 32, Folder 656)
    - Subastavicius, J., 1973 (Box 32, Folder 657)
    - Suhl, Yuri, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 658)
    - Svetova Literatura, 1962-1963 (Box 32, Folder 659)
    - Swallow Press, 1957-1964, undated (Box 32, Folder 660)
    - "T" General, 1930-1975, undated (Box 32, Folder 661-662)
    - Tagliabue, John, 1963, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 663)
    - Taylor, Kent, 1966-1967 (Box 33, Folder 664)
    - Tenth Muse, 1967-1972, undated (Box 33, Folder 665)
    - Terkel, Studs, 1968, undated (Box 33, Folder 666)
    - Terman, Jean, 1957 (Box 33, Folder 667)
    - Third Press, 1972 (Box 33, Folder 668)
    - Third World Press, 1971-1973 (Box 33, Folder 669)
    - Thomas, Don, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 670)
    - Thomas, Lorenzo, 1963 (Box 33, Folder 671)
    - Thompson, Beverly, 1968-1969 (Box 33, Folder 672)
    - Trachtenberg, Alan, 1958-1968, undated (Box 33, Folder 673)
    - Traubel, Grace, 1960-1964 (Box 33, Folder 674)
    - Triem, Eve, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 675)
    - Truesdale, C. W., 1968-1973 (Box 33, Folder 676)
    - Twayne Publishers, 1963-1971 (Box 33, Folder 677)
    - "U" General, 1960-1975, undated (Box 33, Folder 678)
    - U.S. Committee for Cooperation with the Japan Council against A and H Bombs, 1962 (Box 33, Folder 679)
    - University of Buffalo, 1954-1956 (Box 33, Folder 680)
    - University of California, Los Angeles, 1958-1970 (Box 33, Folder 681)
    - University of Kentucky, 1963, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 682)
    - University of Pennsylvania, 1957-1975 (Box 33, Folder 683)
    - University of Washington, 1969 (Box 33, Folder 684)